Hi my name is Dave Andrews, today I'm going to show you some tips on using a laptop computer.
Now the first thing that I would do when using a laptop is to consider the surface that my laptop is going to be sitting on the majority of the time.
It requires that air get up under that laptop in order to blow hot air out and to keep the laptop from overheating.
Another thing to consider when using your laptop is your battery life.
If you are going to be carrying your laptop around with you, you are probably not going to leave it charged up or plugged into the charger all the time.
So you want to consider some things like when you are using a laptop maybe reduce the brightness on the screen a little bit, I'll pull something out so you can see.
That brightness is a little bit less, and I'm using a key combination on the laptop of the function key and on mine it's the f seven and f eight buttons that will increase and then decrease the brightness on that screen.
Now what that's going to do is reduce the amount of energy is used to power your screen on your laptop and possibly make your battery life last longer.
Now my next tip for you is when you are not using your laptop just shut the top on the laptop.
You don't want to leave that laptop on all the time because it will burn in an image on the screen after you know months and months of using it.
And also when you shut the top on your laptop that's going to cause it to go into standby mode.
When you open it back up it will recover from that standby mode.
My name is Dave Andrews and I've just given you some tips on using a laptop.